<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<library>
    <item>
        <name>direct_access_forbidden</name>
        <string>Direct access of this file is forbidden. This file is used for this websites API system.[br /]To
            unprotect this file, uncomment out
        </string>
        <usesBB>true</usesBB>
    </item>
    <item>
        <name>download_no_get</name>
        <string>Please do not directly access this page. This page is to be used when linked to.</string>
        <usesBB>true</usesBB>
    </item>
    <item>
        <name>file_no_accesskey</name>
        <string>This file also does not have a secret accesskey, so it is not possible to access this page.</string>
        <usesBB>true</usesBB>
    </item>
    <item>
        <name>new_install_welcome</name>
        <string>This website's configuration has not yet been created. This will result in a website that does not
            function correctly.[br /]To install your website use the installer package included in the JArD package.[br
            /][br /][b]Warning: [/b]It does not look like you have an install directory uploaded.
        </string>
        <usesBB>true</usesBB>
    </item>
    <item>
        <name>download_no_exist</name>
        <string>The file requested does not exist or encountered an unknown error. Please try again later.</string>
        <usesBB>true</usesBB>
    </item>
    <item>
        <name>api_lockdown</name>
        <string>This website has been set to [dotted]LOCKDOWN_MODE[/dotted]. This means all PHP scripts using the JArD
            API are disabled.
        </string>
        <usesBB>true</usesBB>
    </item>
    <item>
        <name>mysql_connection_error</name>
        <string>Something has gone wrong with the MySQL server's connection with %/FRAMEWORK/%. Maybe trying to refresh
            this page will help?
        </string>
        <usesBB>true</usesBB>
    </item>
    <item>
        <name>db_connection_error</name>
        <string>Oops, it looks like the connection between the mysql server and the mysql database went terribly
            wrong!
        </string>
        <usesBB>true</usesBB>
    </item>
    <item>
        <name>wrong_password</name>
        <string>Sorry the password you have entered does not match the username entered.</string>
        <usesBB>true</usesBB>
    </item>
    <item>
        <name>unknown_username</name>
        <string>Sorry the username you have entered does not match any of them in our database.</string>
        <usesBB>true</usesBB>
    </item>
    <item>
        <name>profile_created</name>
        <string>Your username and other account details have been added to our database. You may not login both game and
            forum using your login details.
        </string>
        <usesBB>true</usesBB>
    </item>
    <item>
        <name>profile_deleted</name>
        <string>Your profile has been deleted. This will mean all your posts will not show up as being posted by you and
            you will no longer be able to login with your old login details.[br]If you wish to reverse this change, we
            have already sent you an email with all the information you will need to get your account back.
        </string>
        <usesBB>true</usesBB>
    </item>
    <item>
        <name>banned_warning</name>
        <string>We are sorry, but your account has been banned from logging into our login server(s). For more
            information we have sent an email to the email you registered with, with all the info you may need to know
            about the reason of your ban.
        </string>
        <usesBB>true</usesBB>
    </item>
    <item>
        <name>muted_warning</name>
        <string>Just before we throw you to the main site, we would just like to say that you have been muted from the
            forum and %SITENAME%. This mute will expire on the %MUTE->EXPIRE%. You will still be allowed to use the
            private message system, but no public messages or comments from you will enter our database.
        </string>
        <usesBB>true</usesBB>
        <disabled>true</disabled>
    </item>
</library>